<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on Dane&#39;s Blog on Travel and Data</title>
    <link>http://danecollins.github.io/categories/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on Dane&#39;s Blog on Travel and Data</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://danecollins.github.io/categories/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lake Nacimiento during the poppy bloom</title>
      <link>http://danecollins.github.io/travel/nacimiento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://danecollins.github.io/travel/nacimiento/</guid>
      <description>With the big rainfalls we have had this year we knew that there would be wildflowers. While spending a few days in Paso Robles we thought we would explore a little and ended up heading over to Lake Nacimiento. It was definitely worth the trip as the wild flowers were out in force.&#xA;While the wild flowers were the highlight of the trip on our way back to the freeway I spotted this great folded sandstone which was completely unexpected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McArthur - Burney Falls State Park</title>
      <link>http://danecollins.github.io/travel/mcarthur/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://danecollins.github.io/travel/mcarthur/</guid>
      <description>The waterfall through the basalt cliff is spectacular. We got to see it late in the afternoon and the sun was not at the best angle but this is a place that is worth going to more than once.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The wonders of the Petrified Forest National Park</title>
      <link>http://danecollins.github.io/travel/petrified-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://danecollins.github.io/travel/petrified-forest/</guid>
      <description>Initially uncertain about what to expect, our visit to the Petrified Forest National Park was a delightful revelation. This expansive park offers more than just a casual glimpse into ancient geology; it provides a captivating landscape filled with petrified wood.&#xA;Why the Petrified Forest is Worth the Visit&#xA;Ample Space to Roam: One of the first things you&amp;rsquo;ll notice is the park&amp;rsquo;s sheer size, allowing you to wander freely and take in the sights of petrified wood scattered all around.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carpinteria State Park: A Beachside Haven</title>
      <link>http://danecollins.github.io/travel/carpinteria/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://danecollins.github.io/travel/carpinteria/</guid>
      <description>Located just south of Santa Barbara, Carpinteria State Park Campground is a perfect destination for anyone looking for a beachside retreat that also offers access to nearby amenities. With campsites situated right on the beach, some with hookups, visitors can enjoy stunning views of the Pacific Ocean and a range of outdoor activities.&#xA;One of the standout features of this campground is its proximity to Carpinteria’s charming downtown area, where visitors can find a variety of restaurants and shops within easy walking distance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Rock Canyon State Park</title>
      <link>http://danecollins.github.io/travel/redrock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://danecollins.github.io/travel/redrock/</guid>
      <description>There are parks that are easy to get to and that are in places where you&amp;rsquo;re likely to go so it&amp;rsquo;s easy to drop in on a trip. This is not one of them. It&amp;rsquo;s East of Bakersfield and North of Lancaster and is really a destination in itself. If you make the trip though you are rewarded by some geology you don&amp;rsquo;t often get to see.&#xA;Cora really enjoyed running around all the rocks.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
